Weee!, Inc. Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: September 8, 2022**

**Introduction**

Welcome to Weee!. Weee! Inc. (Weee!, "we" "us" or "our") operates a network of websites and mobile applications serving multiple cities in the United States. By visiting our website, [https://www.sayweee.com/en](https://www.sayweee.com/en) (the "Site"), using our mobile apps, and accessing the information, resources, services, products, and tools that we provide, you understand and agree to accept and adhere to the Weee! Privacy Policy (hereafter referred to as the "Privacy Policy"), along with the terms and conditions as stated in our [Terms of Service](https://www.sayweee.com/en/about/terms-of-service) which is incorporated herein by reference. If you do not feel comfortable with any part of this Privacy Policy or our Terms, please discontinue use of the Services or engaging with Weee! immediately.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your personal information on our websites and mobile applications, and any other resources, services, products, and tools we provide for you, either directly or indirectly, that link to this Privacy Policy (hereafter, referred to as "Services").

**CONTENTS**

* **1\. Updates to This Privacy Policy**
* **2\. Information We Collect**
* **3\. How We Use Your Information**
* **4\. Sharing and Disclosures of Personal Information**
* **5\. Information for California Residents**
* **6\. Protecting Your Information**
* **7.Access, Correction and Deletion of Your Personal Information**
* **8\. Use of Cookies**
* **9\. Communications Preferences**
* **10.Important Notice for Non-U.S. Residents**
* **11\. Integration of Third-Party Platforms and Services**
* **12\. Children's Privacy**
* **13\. Contacting Us**

**Section 1. Updates to This Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do so, we will provide notice to you by posting it on our website and in our mobile applications, and indicating the date it was modified. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy periodically to familiarize yourself with any modifications. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please reach out to us anytime at[privacy@sayweee.com](http://mailto:privacy@sayweee.com/) or as described in the "Contacting Us" section below.

**Section 2. Information We Collect**

Weee! collects personal information when you interact with our Services. Personal information is any information that identifies or makes an individual identifiable. The definition of personal information (used interchangeably in this Privacy Policy with the term "personal data") depends on the applicable law based on your physical location. Only the definition that applies to your physical location will apply to you under this Privacy Policy. The types of personal information that we may collect about you include, but are not limited to: information you provide to us, information collected automatically about your use of our Services, and information from third parties.

This includes:

* **Account Registration.** We collect basic account information such as your email address, phone number, username and password. We need this information to create your account and it helps secure and provide access to our Services. We also obtain or infer demographic information, as well as profile photos if you choose to upload one. If you use Facebook or another service such as Google or WeChat to register for or log in to the Services (or later connect your accounts), you authorize Facebook or the other service, as the case may be, to share your personal information with us, including your email address, age and publicly available information about you and your Facebook friends, if you use Facebook for registering for the Services. Please note that when you access our Services through social media channels or when you connect our Services to social media services, you are authorizing us to collect, store, and use such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
    
* **Form Submissions and Newsletter Signups.** We collect information that you provide by filling in forms that we make available. This includes when making purchases from our Services or requesting information or assistance. We also collect information relating to our newsletter subscription page, including name and email address. In addition, we collect the email address of others if you refer a friend as part of our Weeebates referral. Please have permission in order to share their information with us.
    
* **Program Participation and Promotions.** We collect information related to your participation in our programs, including our Weee! VIP program, our registered affiliate program, or promotions or surveys.
    
* **Services Usage.** We gather information from the actions you take to recommend, create, communicate and share content. This includes messages you send, posts you create yourself, and the products you mark as favorites or share. In addition, we track social interactions in our Apps (e.g. what you bought, what you loved, and your posts and invites).
    
* **Customer Service and Technical Support.** If you send us support requests or comments you may also provide us with additional information to enable us to contact you and address your feedback, and we may retain such information to enhance our Services and to respond to you.
    
* **Payment Information.** When you purchase products or services from Weee!, you provide our payment processor with your payment information. We currently use third parties to process such payments but may change that in the future.
    
* **Job Applications.** We collect employment- and background-related information provided to us as a part of the job application process.
    
* **Device Permissions.** We collect information relating to your use of features of our Services that may ask you to grant us access to location information, photos, microphone, video camera, or media on your computer or mobile device.

We also collect information automatically as you navigate and interact with our Services. For instance, when you browse our Site, our systems automatically collect information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, domain names, referring and exit pages and URLs, platform type, pages viewed and the order of these page views, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time of your request. Likewise, if you access the Services through a mobile device (e.g., a smart phone or tablet), we may be able to identify the general location of your mobile device, your mobile device's brand, model, operating system, resolution, screen size, system version, mobile network information, and your mobile device's advertising ID.

**Section 3. How We Use Your Information**

Weee! will only use your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy or as disclosed to you prior to such processing taking place. The purposes for which we may use your personal information include:

* **To Provide You Our Services:** providing any services or products that you request or purchase in connection with the Services;
    
* **To Provide You with Service-Related Communications:** contacting you regarding the administration of any features or functions of the Services you have registered to use, and notifying you about changes to our Services, our policies, your program memberships, terms, or any products or services we offer or provide though our Services;
    
* **To Provide Customer Support or to Respond to You:** providing you with notices about your account and responding to your questions or other requests;
    
* **To Send You Marketing and Promotional Emails:** contacting you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you based on the Services that you already use or the offerings that you have already purchased or inquired about, unless you have opted not to receive such information;
    
* **For Internal Use and Services Improvement:** accumulating and reporting aggregate, statistical information in connection with the Services and user activity, including determining which features and services users like best to help us operate, enhance, and improve our Services;
    
* **To Enforce Compliance with Our Agreements or Policies:** keeping you secure and safe while using our Services, which requires us to process your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy to combat spam, malware, malicious activities, fraud, or security risks as part of our ongoing maintenance and enforcement of our security measures, and carrying out our obligations and enforcing our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection;
    
* **To Maintain Legal and Regulatory Compliance:** processing personal information to pay our taxes, fulfill our business obligations, for compliance with employment and recruitment laws, or as necessary to manage risk under applicable law;
    
* **For Customization:** saving your user account, registration and profile data or other personal information (so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit or use the Services); tracking your return visits to and use of the services; tailoring your experience on the Services; and/or otherwise customizing what you see when you visit and use the Services;
    
* **For Research Purposes:** for research purposes and to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients and business partners;
    
* **With Your Consent:** for any other purpose disclosed to you prior to you providing us your personal information or which is reasonably necessary to provide the Services or other related products and/or services requested, with your permission or upon your direction;
    
* **For Employment Purposes:** processing job applications, including to communicate with you and to conduct applicant and employment-related statistical evaluation and record-keeping.

**Section 4. Sharing and Disclosures of Personal Information**

Weee! may share or disclose your personal information in the following circumstances:

* **Within Our Corporate Organization.** We may share your personal information with any subsidiaries and affiliates in order to provide you with the Services and take actions based on your request, as well as for the purpose of management and analysis.
    
* **Service Providers.** We may employ other companies and individuals to facilitate our Services, provide services on our behalf, perform service-related business activities, or assist us in analyzing how our Services are used. These service providers provide us support services such as credit card processing, payment gateways, website hosting, online store platforms, customer relationship management, order fulfillment and shipping, email and postal delivery, analytics, surveys, and marketing services. The service providers have access to your personal information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
    
* **Corporate Transactions.** We may disclose personal information to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about our Services users is among the assets transferred. You agree to and do hereby consent to our assignment or transfer of rights to your personal information.
    
* **Advertising and Marketing.** We may share some personally information with direct mail marketing partners operating a cooperative with other retailers and their customer data to help us: (1) identify products and services that may be of interest to you; and (2) identify new customers with similar interests.
    
* **As Required by Law and to Protect Lawful Interests.** We may disclose your information if we believe that the disclosure is required by law, if we believe that the disclosure is necessary to enforce our agreements or policies, in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g., a court or a government agency), or if we believe that the disclosure will help us protect the rights, property, or safety of Weee! or our customers.
    
* **With Your Consent.** We may disclose your personal information for any purpose with your consent.

Please note that we may disclose, without restriction, aggregated or anonymized information about the users of our Services, which is information that does not identify any specific individual.

**Section 5. Information for California Residents**

This section applies solely to individuals who reside in the State of California. If you are a California resident, you are entitled to request notice of certain information about the user information that we may share with third parties for marketing purposes (e.g., the categories of user information shared, and contact information of applicable third parties), as well as request that we disclose to you what personal information we collect, use, disclose and sell about you, and the right to request deletion of personal information we collect or maintain about you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please mail your written request to Weee! at the physical address below and title your request as follows or in a similar manner: "CCPA – California Resident Request". You also have the right to opt out of the sale of your personal information (as defined by applicable law), which you may exercise by clicking [Do Not Sell My Info](https://sayweee-privacy.my.onetrust.com/webform/5a6677ea-9f57-4a90-bb1f-f77090ae6a03/ae32fcd4-b2bd-4588-a65f-99539c312936), and to not be treated in a discriminatory manner for having exercised your rights regarding your privacy rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA).

As described above, our Services collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or device. In particular, if we acknowledge collection of information below, the Services have collected the following categories of personal information from our consumers within the last twelve (12) months. A listing of the categories of information required to be disclosed by the CCPA is below, and information as to the sources of the information, the purposes of information collection, and how it is shared is described in Sections 2, 3 and 4 of this Privacy Policy, respectively.

| CATEGORY | EXAMPLES | COLLECTED |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers | A real name, alias, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers. | Yes |
| Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)) | A name, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, or any financial information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories. | Yes |
| Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law | Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex, sexual orientation, veteran or military status, genetic information. | No  |
| Commercial information | Records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. | Yes |
| Biometric information | Genetic, physiological, behavioral, and biological characteristics, or activity patterns used to extract a template or other identifier or identifying information. | No  |
| Internet or other similar network activity | Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer's interaction with a website, application, or advertisement. | Yes |
| Geolocation data | Physical location. | Yes |
| Sensory data | Audio, electronic, visual, or similar information. | No  |
| Professional or employment-related information | Current or past job history or performance evaluations. | No  |
| Non-public education information (per the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C.Section 1232g, 34 C.F.R.Part 99)) | Education records. | No  |
| Inferences drawn from other personal information | Profile reflecting a person's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes. | No  |

**Sale of Personal Information Under the CCPA.** In the preceding twelve months we have not sold your personal information, as that term is generally understood, but we recognize that the CCPA defines "personal information" in such a way that making available identifiers linked to you for a benefit may be considered a "sale."

In addition to the "Use of Cookies" section's description for opting out of interest-based advertising and controlling browser settings, California consumers may also use the Digital Advertising Alliance's tool to send requests under the CCPA for a web browser to opt out of the sale of personal information by some or all of that framework's participating companies by accessing the DAA's tool here: [https://www.privacyrights.info/](https://www.privacyrights.info/), or by downloading the DAA's AppChoices mobile application opt-out here: [https://www.privacyrights.info/appchoices](https://www.privacyrights.info/appchoices).

**Rights Under the CCPA.** Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights – Subject to certain exceptions, if you are a California resident you have the right to request a copy of the personal information that we collected about you during the 12 months before your request. Once we receive your request and verify your identity, we will disclose to you:

* The categories of personal information we have collected about you;
* The categories of sources for the personal information we have collected about you;
* Our business or commercial purpose for the information collection;
* The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information;
* The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.
* Deletion Request Rights – You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions.

**Non-Discrimination.** We recognize and respect that you have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment by the business for exercising any of your CCPA rights.

**Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights.** To exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above as a California resident, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by contacting us as described in the "Contacting Us" section below.

**Use of an Authorized Agent to Submit a Request.** Only you or a person you formally authorize to act on your behalf may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information as a California consumer. If you use an authorized agent to submit such a request, we will require written proof that the authorized agent has been authorized to act on your behalf or a copy of the power-of-attorney document granting that right.

**Direct Marketing.** If you are a California resident, you can request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information we have shared with third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. To request a notice, please submit your request by postal mail to the contact information listed below.

**Section 6. Protecting Your Information**

We have implemented reasonable measures designed to help secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL or other encryption technology, or will use our third party payment processors, who will use appropriate security procedures.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where you have chosen a password for access to certain parts of our Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You should not share your password with anyone or reuse your password for any other services.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Service. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Services. If you believe that any of your personal information held by Weee! has possibly been compromised, please contact us immediately as described in the "Contacting Us" section below.

**Section 7. Access, Correction and Deletion of Your Personal Information**

You have the ability to access, correct, and delete your personal information that you shared with us on our Services or through other written or oral means. We are committed so that your personal information is kept accurate and up to date. However, it is up to you to update it with any changes. In most cases, you can review and submit changes to your personal information by logging into the Site and visiting your account profile page. You may also notify us via the information in the "Contacting Us" section below to request access to, or to correct any personal information that you have provided to us. We may not accommodate a request to delete or change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you no longer wish to have your personal information processed, you may request to delete your account (username and password), subject to certain limitations, by contacting us as described below.

**Section 8. Deletion of Your Account**

Upon your request, we will delete your account information in accordance with our data retention and deletion policy and anonymize certain account information as needed.

As a seller of consumer goods, we may be legally obligated or permitted to keep certain information for a longer term. Accordingly, even after receiving your request to delete your account, we may retain some of your information pursuant to legal purposes or business operations (e.g. for legal compliance; tax, accounting, or auditing purposes; to address recall of consumer goods sold on our website; to resolve disputes or otherwise enforce our legal rights; to detect and prevent fraudulent or illegal activity; or investigation necessitated by any of the foregoing).

**Section 9. Use of Cookies**

We use cookies, which deposit small data files stored on your computer or mobile device. We use cookies to distinguish you, identify your interests and your account and its status and settings, to collect usage data, keep track of your preferences and deliver content specific to your interests. Our advertising partners may use cookies and similar technologies to identify and deliver content and advertising specific to your interests, to track the effectiveness of such advertising and to provide and analyze their services. By using our Services you consent to our, and our advertising partners' use of cookies and related technologies, and the sharing of data with our advertising partners.

**Your Choices.** Your browser may provide you with the option to refuse some or all browser cookies. You may also be able to remove cookies from your browser. You can exercise your preferences in relation to cookies served on our Site by taking the steps outlined below.

* _First-Party Cookies._ You can use the browser with which you are viewing this Site to enable, disable or delete cookies. To do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the "Help", "Tools" or "Edit" settings). Please note, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access secure areas of the Site. Also, if you disable cookies other parts of the Site may not work properly. You can find more information about how to change your browser cookie settings at  [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).
    
* _Third-Party Cookies._ Many advertising companies that collect information for interest-based advertising are members of the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) or the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), both of which maintain websites where people can opt out of interest-based advertising from their members. To opt-out of website interest-based advertising provided by each organization's respective participating companies, visit the DAA's opt-out portal available at  [http://optout.aboutads.info/](http://optout.aboutads.info/), or visit the NAI's opt-out portal available at  [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).

To opt-out of data collection for interest-based advertising across mobile applications by participating companies, download the DAA's AppChoices mobile application opt-out offering here: [https://youradchoices.com/appchoices](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices).

More information can also be found here:

* Facebook, whose Data Policy can be found[here](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php).
    
    Google. You can learn more about how Google use's data, and how you can-opt-out, [here](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/).

We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. In addition, most web browsers provide help pages relating to setting cookie preferences. More information may be found for the following browsers here:

**Analytics**. We may use third-party service providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Site. Presently, we use Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google LLC ("Google") that tracks and reports Site traffic. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en). Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics, available at: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**Do Not Track.** Some Internet browsers, such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari, include the ability to transmit "Do Not Track" or "DNT" signals. Since uniform standards for "DNT" signals have not been adopted, our Site does not currently process or respond to "DNT" signals.

**Location-Based Services.** If you enable location-based services on your computer or mobile device in connection with your use of the Services, you expressly consent to Weee! collecting the geolocation (which may include specific longitude and latitude) of your device. This information will be used as set forth in this Privacy Policy, including to locate nearby locations that offer Weee! products and to provide specific advertising content or messages based on your location.

You can withdraw your consent to our use of cookies using your browser settings or your device's limit ad tracking settings. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent. You can do this through your browser. Each browser is different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. You may also be able to control the use of cookies via industry websites such as  [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) or through other functionality which we may have available from time to time. Our current partners include:  
If you disable cookies, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders.

**Section 10. Communications Preferences**

In order to provide service to you, we may send you communications related to your transactions, security, or the administration of this website. From time to time, we may also send you other messages or updates about Weee!, our website, and our other products and offerings. If you do not wish to receive non-transaction or security-related communications from us, you may opt-out by clicking the "unsubscribe" link in the communication or by contacting us as specified in the "Contacting Us" section below.

Please note that "opt-out" and "unsubscribe" requests may not take effect immediately and may take a reasonable amount of time to receive, process and apply, during which time your information shall remain subject to the prior privacy settings.

By downloading and using our mobile applications, you may receive messages, reminders, offers, news, and information from Weee! within the mobile application itself. These "in app" messages are part of our mobile application's functionality but can be adjusted using your device or app settings.

**Section 11. Important Notice for Non-U.S. Residents**

Our services are intended for use in the United States only. The Services and their servers are operated in the United States. Please be aware that your information, including your personal information, may be transferred to, processed, maintained, and used on computers, servers, and systems located where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you choose to use our Website while located outside the United States, you hereby irrevocably and unconditionally consent to such transfer, processing, and use of your information in the United States and elsewhere. If you do not wish for your information to be transferred to, processed, or maintained outside of the country or jurisdiction where you are located, you should immediately cease accessing our Services.

**Section 12. Integration of Third-Party Platforms and Services**

The Services may be linked to, rely on and be integrated with websites, applications, interfaces, services and platforms operated by other companies, including third-party services. The Services may also feature advertisements from these companies. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites, applications, interfaces, services and platforms operated by third parties that are linked to, rely on and/or integrated with the Services or for the privacy practices of third party advertising companies. Once you leave our Services via a link, access a third-party service or click on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policies to determine, among other things, how related companies process personal information they may collect about you. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Weee!.

**Section 13. Children's Privacy**

Weee! Services are not directed toward children under the age of 16, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 16. If a child under 16 provided our Services with personal information, we ask that a parent or guardian contact us as described below so that we may promptly delete the child's information from our record.

**Section 14. Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the information below:

**_Via Mail_**

Weee! Inc.  
47467 Fremont Blvd.  
Fremont, CA 94538

**_Via Email_**

**_Via Phone_**

(510) 358-8960 / (888) 826-0880
